<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | Gian Marco Forghieri</title>
    <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2019</copyright><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://gmforghieri.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey - Cross the first threshold</title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/cross-the-first-threshold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/cross-the-first-threshold/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey - Call to adventure</title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/call-to-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/call-to-adventure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this part I will write about the call to adventure which is about stepping out of the comfort zone,
leaving the ordinary world behind and facing the unknown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As mentioned in the previous post, already in my last year of high school I was greatly dissatisfied and
felt that I am in a closed minded atmosphere which I needed to escape. Even though I did not really have an idea of where to continue,&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hero&#39;s Journey - An Ordinary World</title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/the-ordinary-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gmforghieri.github.io/post/the-ordinary-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this series of blog posts I will attempt to analyze my journey based on the hero myth pattern popularized by Joseph Campbell,
which was influenced by Carl Jung&#39;s work on myth and archetypes also known as the ancient patterns of personality traits that are the shared heritage of the human race.
In other words, the hero&#39;s journey represents the universal human condition of being born into this world, growing, learning, struggling to become an individual, and dying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first part of the story in which we learn about the hero before the real journey begins.
The ordinary world describes the hero&#39;s comfort zone, customs, conditioned beliefs and behaviours.
This is where the hero lives before the journey, thus we learn about his everyday life and get a glimpse about his character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on the above, I will attempt to describe how the ordinary world looked like for me and how certain events might have influenced
who I am today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Coming Soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
