<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Gian Marco Forghieri</title>
    <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://gmforghieri.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2019</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://gmforghieri.github.io/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://gmforghieri.github.io/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://gmforghieri.github.io/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Gian Marco. I am a curious and rebellious individual constantly questioning the status quo and trying to find ways to better myself and make a positive impact in the world. I am a great believer in lifelong learning and self-development; for that reason, I wake up every day with the intent to challenge myself, learn and expand my knowledge and limits.
I finished high school with many questions unanswered, therefore, I went on a journey of self-discovery, to see the world for myself, figure out what I want from my life and explore what I am truly capable of. Since then, I have taken complete ownership of my life and finances, lived in 4 countries, attended 3 higher educational institutions and worked at 4 companies in different roles.
The experiences I have accumulated and books I’ve read made me realize, that our society is flawed in many ways and has an abundance of inefficiencies. I am excited to be learning new things and work on problems that will help change that.
I am currently a 2nd year BSc student in computer science &amp;amp; engineering at TU Delft and also working as a junior full stack software engineer to further refine my programming skills.
I am looking for internship opportunities from 2020 summer onwards, in software development roles with special interest in the following areas:
  • revolutionizing education
  • solving problems and creating economic value in the investment/algorithmic-trading/FinTech scene
  • contributing to a large-scale software product which serves massive amounts of people worldwide&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
